ynetnews.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy and Statement

Welcome to the privacy policy of Yedioth Internet and Yedioth Ahronoth Ltd.

In this privacy policy, we will explain how we use the information we receive or collect, about the internet surfers and users of our applications and websites: ynet website (at: www.ynet.co.il), the premium ynet + site, winwin, ynetnews, other websites related to the ynet site, the ynet application, the ynet+ application, and the Yehdioth Ahronoth newspaper application (hereinafter the “Websites").

If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please immediately stop browsing the Websites and any other use of the Websites.

This privacy policy is binding, and it will apply to any viewing or browsing, uploading of content, or any other use of the Websites, by any person, and by any means, application or device (hereinafter - “Use” and the “Website Users”).

There is no legal obligation to consent to the transmission, collection, production or other use of the information.

In respect to any browsing or other use of the Websites, you voluntarily agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, and to the saving, transmission and production of the information, to the processing and transfer of the information, and any other use of the information as set forth in this policy.

In respect to any surfing or other use of the Website, you represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years of age, or that you use the Websites with the approval of one of your parents (or a guardian responsible for you), and with his agreement to this Privacy Policy in its entirety.

You may contact us by telephone at +972-3-6082222 or at Yedioth Internet Customer Service Department, 1 Noah Moses Rishon Le Zion; Fax number: 03-6932466 (note: for customer service); or by email at [service@y-i.co.il](mailto:service@y-i.co.il) regarding any questions about this Privacy Policy, and for the purpose of exercising your rights, or in any other matter relating to the information or information security 

The privacy policy refers to both women and men, and it is worded in the male gender for convenience only.

This Privacy Policy was last updated in the month of August 2019.

In some of the Websites we will request that you enter details, in the framework of a registration process, or so that you may use various services: games, promotions, sale and purchase of products, forums, various networking activities, etc. (hereinafter - the "Services"). We will store the information you enter in our databases and use it for these purposes:

1\. Full name, identity certificate number, telephone number, contact details, address, email address

We will use this information 

to contact you, to enable you to use the various Websites and Services and to improve your experience of using these Websites and Services, to send you updates and direct mail, marketing information, newsletters, and promotional offers that may be of interest to you, for analysis purposes, segmentation and improvement of the Services and in to enable you to post information on Websites (as part of Services that offer this option). 

2\. Details of Means of Payment

In some of the Websites we will request that you enter your credit card details, or other means of payment. We will use this information, however, only for making purchases on the Websites, and for no other purpose or matter.

3\. Details of products that you purchased or sold, pictures, talkbacks and other content that you will publish on the websites

On some of the Websites, you can post and upload messages, photos, comments (talkbacks), and other content. We will use this information to enable you to publish the content and use the Websites, for monitoring, management, analysis, segmenting and improving the experience of using the Websites, to tailor the content and advertisements displayed to you, for marketing purposes, and in order to enable you to publish information on the Websites that permit this.

Information that we collect about you:

We produce and store information about users of the Websites and use it for these purposes:

1\. Offers and Services that interested you, monitoring surfing habits, usage data, information and advertisements you have viewed, web pages you have browsed, products you have purchased, fields of interest

We will use this information to tailor the content and advertisements displayed to you to your preferences and interests, in order to send you updates and direct mailing, marketing information, and advertising offers that may be of interest to you, as well as for monitoring, segmenting, managing and improving your experience using the Websites.

For further details regarding our use of cookies and other monitoring means, see the section regarding cookies hereafter in this policy.

2\. Location data, course of traffic, IP address, device ID number, device type and settings, language, browser type

We will use this information to tailor the content and advertisements displayed to you to your preferences and interests, to send you updates and direct mailing, marketing information, and advertising offers that may be of interest to you, as well as for monitoring, segmenting, managing and improving your experience using the Websites.

If you use our application, location data will be collected even when the application is not running (by using GPS signals or other information sent from the device where the application is installed). You can prevent the collection of location data from your device at any time by changing the settings in accordance with the device manufacturer's instructions.

3\. Information from advertisers and from our business partners

We may receive information about you, from our advertisers and business partners, and of other entities and companies in the Yedioth Ahronoth group. We will use this information in order to tailor the content and advertisements displayed to you to your preferences and interests, to send you updates and direct mailing, marketing information, and advertising offers that may be of interest to you, as well as for monitoring, segmenting, managing and improving your experience using the Websites.

4\. Information from social networks: details, pictures and profile picture, age range, gender, email address and ID number (given to each user), and additional information, according to your agreement with social networking sites

You can use some of the Websites through a link to your Facebook account, or links to accounts on other social networks. In these cases, information about you may be transmitted to us according to the terms of use and permissions you have set in your accounts. We will use this information to tailor the content and advertisements displayed to you, your preferences and interests, to send you updates and direct mailing, marketing information, and advertising suggestions that may be of interest to you, as well as for monitoring, segmenting, managing and improving your site experience.

The information identified about you will be collected, produced and stored in our databases.

Our Websites include links to sites that we do not control (hereinafter - the "Linked Sites"), which may collect, use and produce information about their users. Providing details, and any other use of the Linked Sites, is subject to the Terms of Use and Privacy of the Linked Sites, and they are not under our control or responsibility.

Saving and processing information about you is based on the need to enable you to use the Websites and to provide you with the Services, on your consent, or on our legitimate interests in operating the Websites.

Transferring Information to Third Parties:

For the purposes and uses set forth in this Privacy Policy, and to support and operate the Websites (including through "Cloud Services"), we may transfer information about you, to companies and other entities in the Yedioth Ahronoth Group, as well as to other entities and various service providers - in Israel and abroad.

We may pass on information to third parties, also in these cases:

1\. In the event that you publish the information (in a sale notice, content on your behalf, or in any other publication that you upload to one of our Websites);

2\. In order to tailor third-party advertising and various content for you.

3\. If you purchase products or Services from our trading and content partners, or participate in the activities of these entities, we will transfer to our partners the information they need about you to complete the purchase process or management activity, and maintain contact with you;

4\. In the event that you violate the Terms of Use of the Websites, or the provisions of the subscription agreements to Websites or for Services, or if you perform any actions that appear to be in violation of the law;

5\. In case a dispute arises between you and us, or if we receive a judicial order or regulatory instruction, instructing us to provide the information;

6\. In the event that we organize the activities of the Websites in the framework of another corporation, or merge with another entity, or merge the activities of the Websites with the activities of another entity - provided that the other entity assumes the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

The third parties to whom we may transmit information are:

1\. Our trading and content partners, as well as companies and entities in the Yedioth Ahronoth group, including the various service providers and consultants of the companies and entities in the group.

2\. Entities that will be exposed to the details that you publish on the Websites (for example talkbacks or advertisements to sell a product).

3\. Entities that a judicial body or any regulatory body may order to grant them access to information.

4\. Any entity who shall purchase the activities of the Site, or shall merge with a corporation from Yedioth Group, provided that it is subject to this Privacy Policy.

In any event that we transmit information about you outside the borders of Israel, the transfer of the information will be performed in accordance with the terms of the law and this policy.

We will use the contact information you enter (by registering for Services or to the Websites, by purchasing or selling products, uploading and publishing content on your behalf, or in any other case where you enter contact information), in order to keep in touch with you, to offer and send you various marketing content from various entities, direct mailing, newsletters , updates, advertising, and to notify you of various notices regarding Services and the Websites (hereinafter - "Mail").

The Mail will be sent to you via e-mail, pop-up notifications or push notifications, SMS messages, and any other means of communication.

If you do not wish to receive advertising mail, you may contact us and request that your name be removed from the mailing list, by clicking on a link that appears in each e-mail message sent to you, or by contacting: Yedioth Customer Service Department, 1 Noah Moses Street Rishon Lezion ; or by email, at [service@y-i.co.il](mailto:service@y-i.co.il), or by contacting the service call center at number: 972-3-6082222. We will remove your information from the mailing list, in accordance with your request, the Telecommunications Law (Bezeq and Broadcasting), 5742- 1982, and the Privacy Protection Law, 5742- 1982.

If you use our applications, we will send you warnings, updates and push notifications, including sounds, even when the application is not in use, through the device servers on which the application is installed.

You may, at any time, cancel or update the possibility of receiving push notifications by changing the application settings on your device.

We will keep the information about you during the period that you use our Websites or Services, and afterwards for the purpose of providing the Services, and sending offers and updates, or other mail, in accordance with the terms of this policy.

We will also keep the information about you during the period required to protect and maintain our legal rights, as well as in order to comply with regulatory requirements, the prevention of deception or fraud, enforcement of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use of the Websites.

1\. The right to review the information

You are entitled to review information that was collected about you, that is stored in our databases, and which is identified and associated with you. It is not possible to review information which is not identified and associated with you.

2\. The right to amend information

If you have found that the information stored about you is not correct, complete, clear or updated, it is possible to contact us, in a detailed request to amend or delete the information.

To exercise these rights, please contact us using the contact information provided at the beginning of this document. We will review your application and respond according to the deadlines set in the law. If we refuse your request, you can appeal to the Magistrate's Court, in accordance with the provisions of the law.

3\. The right to cancel consent

You are entitled, at any time, to cancel your consent to receive direct mail, by contacting us with an appropriate request. For additional details, see the chapter on direct mail and advertising notifications.

4\. Additional rights regarding information

You may be entitled to additional rights regarding information about you: rights to delete information, to limit and stop the processing of information, to transfer information to other entities. Inquiries about these issues, or regarding other matters related to this Privacy Policy, can be referred to us through the contact information that appears at the beginning of this document. We will review your inquiry and we will respond accordingly.

Even if we delete, amend information, or grant your request in any other manner, we will in any case continue to keep information we require for managing the Websites and our businesses, including documenting operations, as well as information required to defend and protect our legal rights, or for complying with regulatory requirements, to prevent deception or fraud, and for the enforcement of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use of the Websites.

For complaints regarding your rights or regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact the Privacy Protection Authority at the e-mail address: [PPA@justice.gov.il](mailto:PPA@justice.gov.il)

We invest a lot of effort to protect information and implement various information security systems and procedures. However, our protection and information security systems are not completely immune to all unauthorized penetration or access, and they do not provide absolute protection. We will not be held liable for any damage you may incur as a result of such penetration, unauthorized use, or theft of information from our databases or Websites.

Any use of the various Websites, of content uploaded to Websites and content related to them - could expose you to a variety of dangers associated with using the internet: computer or mobile phone penetration, viruses, malware, etc. Use of the Websites, of the various Services, and the content uploaded to the Websites or the content related to them is under your sole responsibility. We recommend that you install adequate security software and security means before using the Websites and the Services.

The Websites and Services include and use "cookies", "web beacons" pixels, and other systems that collect information and monitor the use of the Websites.

"Cookies" are strings of letters and numbers that are stored in the computer's memory (or device) which allows to store information about you. Some cookies will expire when you finish surfing and close your browser software, and others will be saved in your computer (or device) memory.

The cookies contain information about your surfing habits, the pages you have visited, the length of time you spent on the Websites, where you came from to the Websites, sections and information you wish to see when entering the site, monitoring your surfing and activity habits, details of your ISP, IP address, device location, and more.

The cookies are used for various purposes: gathering statistics, verifying details, adjusting the site to your personal preferences, monitoring surfing habits and activities, surfing history, characterizing your usage of the Websites, improving the service and user experience, advertising and marketing tailored to your preferences, information security, and other purposes.

Some cookies are necessary for the proper operation of the site, some are used for control, evaluation and analysis purposes, and some are used to personalize the marketing and advertising content displayed to you.

Some of the cookies and other systems that operate on the Websites are operated by third parties or as part of the service provided by those third parties in the framework of the Websites. Any use made by these third parties, cookies, web beacons, or any other similar technology, is governed by their privacy policy.

Deleting Cookies and Stopping the Use of Them:

You can delete, or completely stop using cookies by changing the settings in your internet browser. Disabling cookies may harm your possibility of using from using some of the Websites and Services, as well as the quality of surfing and other operations on other websites. In some cases, deleting cookies will require you to re-enter your username and password before logging in to the various Services. For more details about cookies, and the different options for disabling or deleting cookies, please refer to these links, depending on the type of browser you use:

Google Chrome browser:

<https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>

Microsoft Internet Explorer Browser:

<https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/278835/how-to-delete-cookie-files-in-internet-explorer>

Mozilla Firefox browser:

<https://support.mozilla.org/en/kb/%D7%9E%D7%97%D7%99%D7%A7%D7%AA%20%D7%A2%D7%95%D7%92%D7%99%D7%95%D7%AA>

Apple Safari Browser:

<https://support.apple.com/en-il/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac>

Setting Cookie Settings in the Websites:

You can determine and set what types of cookies will be activated during your use of the Websites, and which cookies you refuse to accept.

To set and adjust cookie settings on your site, according to your preferences, click here: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

 Publisher Common ID – Opt-Out

The Publisher Common ID is a cookie that can be utilized by multiple advertisers in order to provide relevant advertising. You may opt-out of receiving this id.

To opt-out Publisher Common ID settings click here: Opt-Out

For more information and other external Opt-Out options:

NAI – https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/

DAA – http://optout.aboutads.info/Other systems that operate in the Websites:

Other systems operate in the Websites which collect information about users, monitor their activities, and some of them also help manage the advertisements on the Websites, including: pixels, "web beacons" and other means. These tools monitor site usage, scope of use, frequency of use, access sources, and other details. The information collected through these tools is designed to tailor the content and advertisements displayed to you to your preferences and to the fields of your interest, as well as for the purposes of analyzing, managing and improving the experience of using the Websites, segmenting research and monitoring.

Some of the advertisements shown to you on Websites are run by third parties. The use of these tools by companies to monitor the activity of surfers is detailed in the privacy policies of those companies.

One of the systems that operates in Websites is the Google Analytics system, which collects information about users' surfing habits. For more details on this system, please see these links: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=iw>, and: <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html>. For options on limiting this system, see the link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

Another system operating on the Websites is Taboola, which collects information about users' surfing habits, and the content offered for viewing is tailored to their preferences. For more details on this system, please see the link: [https://popup.taboola.com/en/?template=colorbox&utm_source=ynet-ynet-:&utm_medium=referral&utm_content=thumbnails-c:Below%20Main%20Column%20Thumbnails](https://popup.taboola.com/en/?template=colorbox&utm_source=ynet-ynet-:&utm_medium=referral&utm_content=thumbnails-c:Below%20Main%20Column%20Thumbnails)

We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time. The binding version of this Privacy Policy is the latest version displayed on the Websites, and you accept and agree to the Privacy Policy including all of its clauses, including any amendments and updates thereof. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, an appropriate notice will be posted on the Websites’ home pages. Please review this page from time to time to check the latest and most binding version of this Privacy Policy.
